popstar.com 2008-02-16

# Popstar.com » Corporate Website » Privacy Policy

Don't see your favorite celebrity in the list to the right?  
Just start typing their name below!

## **Privacy Policy** for Popstar.com

## 

World Digital Group provides this Privacy Policy because we value your right to privacy.

This Policy is effective as of November 18, 2007 and governs the collection of personal information through our websites on or after this date.  This Policy describes the types of information we may collect from visitors and how that information is used.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully before providing us with any personal information.  If you have any questions or concerns about this Policy, please know that we will handle your requests with care.  You may [Contact Us](http://corp.popstar.com/Contact_Us) at any time to discuss this Privacy Policy.

###  **Information We Collect** from Unregistered Users

### 

The information we collect from unregistered users is limited.  We log your IP address in order to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our websites, and to track usage statistics.  Your IP address may vary each time you visit, or it may stay the same.  It would be extremely difficult for us to identify you through your IP address, and we make no attempt to do so.

If you reached our website by clicking on a link or advertisement on another website, we may log that information as well.  We may place a small "cookie" file on your computer's hard drive.  A cookie may contain information that allows us to track your path through our website and to determine whether you have visited us before.  You may elect not to accept cookies by changing settings in your browser.

Unless you register with us, cookies we place on your computer will not contain personally identifiable information.  We may use cookies to help us understand how visitors use our website, and to help us to improve our website.  All of this information is collected and used only in the aggregate.  This means that your information is compiled with that of others to determine common themes among our visitors.

###  **Information We Collect** from Registered Users

### 

You can register at some of our websites to take advantage of personalization features.  If you choose to register with us, it may allow you access to unique features of our websites.  For example, you may post comments, participate in forums, and create your own profile at Popstar.com.  At certain sites, you can receive newsletters and other information.

If you register with us, we will collect personal information from you in addition to the non-personal information described above.  Such personal information may include your name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, travel preferences, username and password, as well as contact information for other people that you provide to us.

The information we collect may vary, but we only collect the information that you manually enter into our forms or otherwise authorize us to collect.  We may store all or some of that information in a cookie file on your hard drive, so that our system will recognize you each time you visit our website.  In that way, we can save your preferences between visits and present you with a customized website each time you visit.

To improve services and enhance personalization, we may periodically obtain information about you from other independent third-party sources and add it to your registration information.  Additionally, authorized personnel may update your registration information to accurately reflect any new information included in communications received from you.

If you reach our website through one of our partners and you choose to register with us, we may be required to give our partner your registration information.

###  **How We Use** the Personal Information We Collect

### 

Registering allows you to personalize our website so that it is more useful to you.  It also allows you to log into our website automatically each time you visit, rather than manually typing your username and password every time, although this may not always be the case.  In order to protect your personal information, logging in will be required to access your private information.

We may use your personal information to periodically contact you with news or important information, to provide you with other information or invitations related to your membership, and to request your feedback on our website.  In addition to these periodic updates, we may email you additional marketing materials that you have requested.  These might include opt-in newsletters and partner offers.

You may opt-out of any or all marketing communications in any commercial email we send to you; opt-out links are provided in all emails.  You may also opt-out by changing your preferences if provided by the website.  And finally, you always have the option to [Contact Us](http://corp.popstar.com/Contact_Us) with an opt-out request and we will honor it as quickly as possible.

We may also use certain information that you provide in order to present you with advertising that you may find interesting.  This benefits both of us.  It benefits us because advertising helps pay the bills, and we can charge our advertisers more if they know that their ads have been sufficiently targeted.  It benefits you because you see advertising that is more likely to be of interest to you.

Probably most importantly, advertising permits us to offer you a broader range of free services.

###  **Disclosure of Your Personal Information** to Other Parties

### 

We may share some of your personally identifiable information with our parent company, subsidiaries, and sister companies.  We do not place restrictions on the use of your personal information by our parent company, subsidiaries, or affiliates, but we do require that they treat your information with as much care as they would treat their own information.

These entities must also comply with applicable laws governing the transmission of promotional communications.  Under the CAN SPAM Act of the United States, they must give you an opportunity in any such email that they send to you to choose not to receive such promotional email messages in the future.  If you feel your rights under this Act have been violated, please visit [www.ftc.gov/spam](http://www.ftc.gov/spam/).

We also may share your personal information with third parties engaged in providing services to us, such as market research firms, marketing services providers, and advertising agencies.  We require such parties to agree to use any such personally-identifiable data solely for the purpose of providing the specified services we have requested from them.

###  **Disclosure of Your Personal Information** to Government Agencies

### 

We must cooperate with legal authorities, and may in some circumstances be required to disclose personally identifiable information in response to requests from law enforcement authorities, or in response to a subpoena or other legal process.  We may turn over information about you if we believe we must in order to prevent a violation of the law.

By using our website, you automatically agree to be bound by the terms of our Privacy Policy, and thus implicitly consent to our doing so, and at our sole discretion.  You also consent to our disclosing information about you in the course of legal proceedings if we are legally required to do so, if we reasonably believe that doing so may mitigate our liability, or if doing so will assist us in enforcing our legal rights.

We also may share your information in connection with a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, and in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.

###  **Changes** to Our Privacy Policy

### 

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy should we deem it advisable to do so.

If we make material changes that will affect personal information we have already collected from you, we will make every reasonable effort to notify you of the changes, and to give you the opportunity to ammend or cancel your registration.  We take your privacy seriously; please don't hesitate to [Contact Us](http://corp.popstar.com/Contact_Us) with any questions or concerns you may have.
